<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Charles Ancheta</title>
    <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Charles Ancheta</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Charles Ancheta. MIT</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:21:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://charles.thyck.top/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025-02-06</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:21:04 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/06/</guid>
      <description>I got too deep into refactoring and worked past 9 PM 😭&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s Friday tomorrow anyway, so maybe I could get off early once I&amp;rsquo;ve done all of the important tasks.&#xA;Today is Jherzey and Jesse&amp;rsquo;s last day in Cancun so I&amp;rsquo;m going to accompany Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s dad to the airport to pick them up. Might grab some food after that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-02-05 &amp; what happened for the past 2 weeks</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:08:59 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/05/</guid>
      <description>Well, that was short-lived. My last post was 17 days ago. Maybe the fact that I made an actual blog post made this too high-effort. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for Jherzey reminding me about my website, I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have started again. Here we go&amp;hellip;&#xA;The past 2 weeks was consumed by tons of distractions, with no opportunity to get bored. I binge-watched Over Run Over on YouTube, and once that was done, binge-watched Trauma Code on Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-18 &amp; 2025-01-19 (Weekend)</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/18-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:18:44 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/18-19/</guid>
      <description>Been sleeping too much on weekends recently. I planned on going out to downtown on Saturday but woke up at 4:30 pm. I just did flashcards, watched some YouTube, and went back to sleep for 12 hours again.&#xA;Today I did go out tubing and eat out with the Gen Z gang.&#xA;This weekend was mostly just watching the interactions between American and Chinese people on 小红书 (Rednote).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-16</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 02:19:01 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/16/</guid>
      <description>Finally got unblocked at a task at work. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I&amp;rsquo;m done though.&#xA;I went to Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s by walking just like the previous days, but didn&amp;rsquo;t know there was a snows squall. That made the walk pretty interesting. I had to go back home and actually bundle up to cover my face.&#xA;After shovelling, I spent 3 hours with Devin to solve a false LSP error on some embedded C toolchain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-15</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:28:03 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/15/</guid>
      <description>Been consistently waking up at 9am which is good in a way because I&amp;rsquo;m being consistent, but bad in a way because it&amp;rsquo;s so late. My alarm clocks are failing me for some reason.&#xA;I had to slowly clear out the 239 cards to review throughout the day, and now I have 244 cards for tomorrow. It&amp;rsquo;s really going to be a grind this week but I only have 425 new cards out of 1210.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-14</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:53:31 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/14/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 9am again today. No worries though, since the rest of my day wasn&amp;rsquo;t wasted.&#xA;I finally followed my scheduled tasks, limiting my Anki review to only 1 hour today. That meant fewer new cards today, but at least I didn&amp;rsquo;t waste any more time with it and lightened up my review load to only 239 cards for tomorrow.&#xA;I also got the chance to get some physical activity:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-11 &amp; 12 (Weekend)</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 01:16:52 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/11-12/</guid>
      <description>Gonna have to combine these two because I forgot what I did already aside from the times I went out 😭.&#xA;I slept for half the day for both days and just planned our trip.&#xA;Saturday: Unlimited K-BBQ at Ginseng with Jherzey and Ate Mup. I could&amp;rsquo;ve eaten a lot more but tried to hold back.&#xA;Sunday: Jerusalem Shawarma and Krispy Kreme with Yahya and Kyle.&#xA;Lots of cramming on flashcards as well, but not as much as today (Monday).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIL: Beans Etymology</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:50:18 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/beans/</guid>
      <description>Being a Tagalog speaker and a language learner, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in etymology of Tagalog words. The obvious influences are Spanish and English, but there&amp;rsquo;s also a lot from Hokkien and Malay.&#xA;Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to list out some words that I find interesting:&#xA;Linggo (Sunday; week) - All the days in Tagalog are directly borrowed from Spanish one to one, except for Sunday (domingo). Apparently it could be from Malay minggu which came from Portuguese domingo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-10</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:39:54 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/10/</guid>
      <description>I actually got up at 6 and felt a lot more motivated today. The fact that I was probably around only 70% productivity the day before meant that I had to go ham today. I finally got around starting my daily/weekly planner (and actually following it).&#xA;Also the fact that I also got approved for my PH vacation gave me a lot more motivation.&#xA;Walked to Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s place while it was raining and super slippery outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-09</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:36:26 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/09/</guid>
      <description>This was the day that I got up at 6 but stayed in bed until 9 😭 so much for waking up early.&#xA;I ate a small clove of garlic in the morning and it was pretty spicy. Tried eating a bigger one and it gave me a crazy heartburn.&#xA;Had a CitySync discussion with Michael before he leaves for Vietnam.&#xA;I also tried out Reaper but didn&amp;rsquo;t get too far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-08</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:02:58 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/08/</guid>
      <description>Woke up early today and did cardio. Almost puked but the cold shower afterwards hit different.&#xA;Also super locked in at work.&#xA;Had K-BBQ at home for dinner with pork belly and organ meats.&#xA;I asked Jherzey to help me skin the cat and it definitely scared her. I did more after she left but my right shoulder started hurting. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to take it easy on the shoulder exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-07</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:32:24 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/07/</guid>
      <description>Pretty productive day!&#xA;Found a beat for focusing at work so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to sit in silence anymore.&#xA;I also tried out some online shopping haul with Jherzey after work before eating momos.&#xA;Just now, I set up Anki with Cantonese flashcards. I picked one without Chinese characters so I actually have to associate sounds to meaning.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been consistently waking up at 7 which means that I can finally get to sleep early (which is why I&amp;rsquo;m actually able to write before midnight now).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Background music while working</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:19:11 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/music/</guid>
      <description>Finally found some appropriate background music for when I&amp;rsquo;m working.&#xA;My peers used to always ask me what I listen to while working on my computer, and they&amp;rsquo;re always shocked to find out that I work in silence. I used to unironically listen to lofi hip hop mix 📚 beats to relax/study to but I get too sleepy. When I listen to music I actually like listening to, I get too distracted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-04</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:14:44 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/04/</guid>
      <description>Slept pretty much until the afternoon and then worked on CitySync stuff.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s already Sunday so I basically skipped 2 days of journalling. I definitely need to streamline this process. I could try using Obsidian for easier journalling and then automate the publishing process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-03</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:36 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/03/</guid>
      <description>Hung out with the Gen Z gang today (actually millennials).&#xA;Walked around downtown at -20°C which was fun.&#xA;Went hotpot and Hanjan which basically broke resolutions 1 &amp;amp; 3 but it&amp;rsquo;s all good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-02</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:01:29 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/02/</guid>
      <description>I got my passport today so I am now legally allowed to leave the country 😌&#xA;I think I should start scheduling my off-work hours because I&amp;rsquo;m bad at time management and get distracted easily. It&amp;rsquo;s already past midnight that I&amp;rsquo;m writing on the journal.&#xA;EDIT:&#xA;I forgot to add why I wanted to do this in the first place. I found an old notebook of mine from 5+ years ago that had this entry:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 11:50:00 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>Q1 Goals Some goals specific to my vacation this March, but also probably good to keep up for the rest of the year.&#xA;Lose weight (~5kg) - going to a wedding Brush up on Chinese - going to HK Not really required to get around, but one time I tried ordering bubble tea and couldn&amp;rsquo;t even say what I wanted Try to eat out less Lines up with Goal 1 and 2, since I&amp;rsquo;m going on a trip and need to save up The rest of the year The most generic resolutions you&amp;rsquo;ll find.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Worst Semester so Far</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/my-worst-semester-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:42:26 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/my-worst-semester-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Fall 2023 was my first semester coming back after being out of school for 16 months (I tried taking CHINA 101 in Fall 2022 but dropped it after a week).&#xA;Because of that, I have forgotten how to study. Both midterms and finals went pretty horribly. It&amp;rsquo;s not even that I don&amp;rsquo;t care about grades anymore, and I definitely could have done better if I just did the practice exams thoughtfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My domain expired 😭</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/expired-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/expired-domain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I hope my &lt;del&gt;namesake&lt;/del&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; pianist &lt;a href=&#34;https://anchetamusic.wordpress.com/about/&#34;&gt;Charles&#xA;Ancheta&lt;/a&gt; claims it back eventually.&#xA;&amp;lsquo;charlesancheta.com&amp;rsquo; used to redirect to his Facebook page before I registered&#xA;the domain as mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Static Website - Part 1: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/static-website-setup/part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 23:04:45 -0600</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/static-website-setup/part-1/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I help a friend set up a website for a business. Today, I had another talk with a friend about building a portfolio website and he asked me for a few resources. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a comprehensive one that outlines all the required steps so I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best.&#xA;What is a static website? From ChatGPT:&#xA;Basically:&#xA;Static - no server-side logic, cheaper Dynamic - with server-side logic, more expensive What makes a (static) website Setting up a static website is basically free these days, maybe a few dollars a year if you want a custom domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIL: Parallel `make`</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/parallel-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/parallel-make/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always kind of known about the &lt;code&gt;-j&lt;/code&gt; flag for &lt;code&gt;make&lt;/code&gt;, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know&#xA;that &lt;strong&gt;it just works&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Deleted My NPM Packages</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/i-deleted-my-npm-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:59:18 -0600</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/i-deleted-my-npm-packages/</guid>
      <description>I deleted all 4 of my NPM packages today. It has been over a year since I&amp;rsquo;ve last updated them, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to add any more clutter to the system.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought that having published open source code meant something, but then I realized that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if it&amp;rsquo;s not useful.&#xA;Learning how to package libraries and applications was a good experience, though, and I would probably publish stuff IF/WHEN I have actually solved a need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/pou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 21:04:23 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/pou/</guid>
      <description>You might have to zoom in a little bit to see these bad boys. They sing a just-intonated major pentatonic scale from a low fifth to a high sixth. Just enough notes to play Auld Lang Syne. Click/tap on a Pou to play a note1.&#xA;Keyboard controls: z,x,a,s,d,q,w for the notes, space for confetti.&#xA;Pou won&#39;t show up without JavaScript :(&#xA;Toggle Confetti It&amp;rsquo;s not as responsive on mobile sadly :(&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replicating My Linux Workflow on Windows</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/replicating-my-linux-workflow-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:49:52 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/replicating-my-linux-workflow-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>A new co-op position meant new hardware1, and a new technology stack to learn. Unfortunately, that includes having to use Windows. Coming back to Windows after almost 2 full years on Linux, it felt like I forgot how to use a computer. All the keyboard shortcuts that my hands were used to would do funny things like lock my laptop. I just wanted my shell, my terminal, and my tiling window manager back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Migrated to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/why-i-migrated-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:50:15 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/why-i-migrated-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aside from the fact that Hugo is &lt;em&gt;Blazingly Fast™&lt;/em&gt;, I had a few problems with&#xA;Docusaurus/the whole JS ecosystem that made it hard for me to keep updating my&#xA;website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Interfaces give me a reason to live again</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/go-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 03:52:09 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/go-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I made a meme about Go being my new favourite language (replacing TypeScript) and I just want to share a satisfying moment I had recently.&#xA;The Task In the previous iteration of my website1, I have a few lines in my config that fetches information about my published NPM packages to be rendered on the Projects page. I wanted to do the same for my new website, outputted as a Markdown table, which can be easily imported into the page with readFile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Log: Boboman - Day 4</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-4/</guid>
      <description>I feel like the hardest part of writing this game would be the enemy logic. That&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m putting it off for as long as possible! Today I implemented map generation, randomly placing boxes sufficiently far enough from players.&#xA;I also added controls for other players, which reminded me of my local multiplayer experience with Boxhead. I miss having multiple people on play a single keyboard. These days it would be awkward to play that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Log: Boboman - Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Feeling good today. I got to fix the collision bug that was happening yesterday. It actually had to do with the collision lifecycle, so to make the player detectable, I decoupled the check from the lifecycle of the bomb. Because of this, I could revert the player&amp;rsquo;s bomb timer to normal. Moving away from a project and letting your brain sit on a problem for a while really does wonders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Log: Boboman - Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-2/</guid>
      <description>MAJOR BUG ALERT!!&#xA;Apparently my collision logic for the bombs weren&amp;rsquo;t going to hold up. Every time a bomb explodes, there is a small time window where you can place a bomb and the bomb would not recognize the player, making it a &amp;ldquo;not new&amp;rdquo; bomb. Because of that, the player gets pushed off right away and could end up in the weirdest of places.&#xA;After hours of debugging I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really solve it because of how the collision library orders the entity updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Log: Boboman - Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/dev-log/boboman/day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been heavily configuring my text editor, Neovim, which means that I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing a lot of Lua. I do&#xA;find it enjoyable, even without having any tooling initially, so I wanted to give game development and&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://love2d.org&#34;&gt;Love2D&lt;/a&gt; a try. I just finished&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sheepolution.com/learn/book/contents&#34;&gt;Sheepolution&amp;rsquo;s How to LÖVE&lt;/a&gt; book on Love2D, and felt prepared to make&#xA;my first game from scratch. As per Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s request, I&amp;rsquo;m creating a Bomberman clone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bye bye Netlify</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/bye-bye-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/bye-bye-netlify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was short trial, but GitHub Pages just works better for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendship Ended with TypeScript, now Go is My Best Friend</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/friendship-ended/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/friendship-ended/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Friendship ended&#34; src=&#34;https://charles.thyck.top/post/friendship-ended/friendship-ended.webp&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIL: My actual height</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/my-actual-height/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/til/my-actual-height/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I learned what my actual height was (at least at the time of writing). For a few years now I&amp;rsquo;ve always kind of&#xA;just stuck with 170 cm because that&amp;rsquo;s what was in my driver&amp;rsquo;s license when I got it 5 years ago (I really need to pass&#xA;the road test this year). I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure if that was right at the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my website! I am Charles, a Computer Engineering Student working as a Full Stack Web Developer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
