<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Charles Ancheta</title>
    <link>https://charles.thyck.top/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Charles Ancheta</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Charles Ancheta. MIT</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:21:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://charles.thyck.top/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025-02-06</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:21:04 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/06/</guid>
      <description>I got too deep into refactoring and worked past 9 PM 😭&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s Friday tomorrow anyway, so maybe I could get off early once I&amp;rsquo;ve done all of the important tasks.&#xA;Today is Jherzey and Jesse&amp;rsquo;s last day in Cancun so I&amp;rsquo;m going to accompany Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s dad to the airport to pick them up. Might grab some food after that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-02-05 &amp; what happened for the past 2 weeks</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:08:59 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/02/05/</guid>
      <description>Well, that was short-lived. My last post was 17 days ago. Maybe the fact that I made an actual blog post made this too high-effort. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for Jherzey reminding me about my website, I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have started again. Here we go&amp;hellip;&#xA;The past 2 weeks was consumed by tons of distractions, with no opportunity to get bored. I binge-watched Over Run Over on YouTube, and once that was done, binge-watched Trauma Code on Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-18 &amp; 2025-01-19 (Weekend)</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/18-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:18:44 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/18-19/</guid>
      <description>Been sleeping too much on weekends recently. I planned on going out to downtown on Saturday but woke up at 4:30 pm. I just did flashcards, watched some YouTube, and went back to sleep for 12 hours again.&#xA;Today I did go out tubing and eat out with the Gen Z gang.&#xA;This weekend was mostly just watching the interactions between American and Chinese people on 小红书 (Rednote).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-17</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 02:20:26 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/17/</guid>
      <description>Drinking black coffee every day was starting to give me mouth sores. I had to use powdered creamer today.&#xA;Remember a few days ago when I said I was going to limit Anki time? I failed to stop myself again.&#xA;To be fair, probably half of flashcard time today was spent making dim sum flashcards. I actually had to do some research in Cantonese wikipedia because some of the items had weird or missing translations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-16</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 02:19:01 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/16/</guid>
      <description>Finally got unblocked at a task at work. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I&amp;rsquo;m done though.&#xA;I went to Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s by walking just like the previous days, but didn&amp;rsquo;t know there was a snows squall. That made the walk pretty interesting. I had to go back home and actually bundle up to cover my face.&#xA;After shovelling, I spent 3 hours with Devin to solve a false LSP error on some embedded C toolchain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-15</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 01:28:03 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/15/</guid>
      <description>Been consistently waking up at 9am which is good in a way because I&amp;rsquo;m being consistent, but bad in a way because it&amp;rsquo;s so late. My alarm clocks are failing me for some reason.&#xA;I had to slowly clear out the 239 cards to review throughout the day, and now I have 244 cards for tomorrow. It&amp;rsquo;s really going to be a grind this week but I only have 425 new cards out of 1210.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-14</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:53:31 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/14/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 9am again today. No worries though, since the rest of my day wasn&amp;rsquo;t wasted.&#xA;I finally followed my scheduled tasks, limiting my Anki review to only 1 hour today. That meant fewer new cards today, but at least I didn&amp;rsquo;t waste any more time with it and lightened up my review load to only 239 cards for tomorrow.&#xA;I also got the chance to get some physical activity:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-13</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 01:24:54 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/13/</guid>
      <description>Productive day at work despite waking up at 9am.&#xA;I think I have really overdone the flashcards now.&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t even have the vocabulary that actually matters, which are dim sum items.&#xA;But I think I&amp;rsquo;m making good progress on the new cards. I could probably be exposed to the entire deck by the end of the month. I&amp;rsquo;m just hoping I retain them until March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-11 &amp; 12 (Weekend)</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 01:16:52 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/11-12/</guid>
      <description>Gonna have to combine these two because I forgot what I did already aside from the times I went out 😭.&#xA;I slept for half the day for both days and just planned our trip.&#xA;Saturday: Unlimited K-BBQ at Ginseng with Jherzey and Ate Mup. I could&amp;rsquo;ve eaten a lot more but tried to hold back.&#xA;Sunday: Jerusalem Shawarma and Krispy Kreme with Yahya and Kyle.&#xA;Lots of cramming on flashcards as well, but not as much as today (Monday).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-10</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:39:54 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/10/</guid>
      <description>I actually got up at 6 and felt a lot more motivated today. The fact that I was probably around only 70% productivity the day before meant that I had to go ham today. I finally got around starting my daily/weekly planner (and actually following it).&#xA;Also the fact that I also got approved for my PH vacation gave me a lot more motivation.&#xA;Walked to Jherzey&amp;rsquo;s place while it was raining and super slippery outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-09</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:36:26 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/09/</guid>
      <description>This was the day that I got up at 6 but stayed in bed until 9 😭 so much for waking up early.&#xA;I ate a small clove of garlic in the morning and it was pretty spicy. Tried eating a bigger one and it gave me a crazy heartburn.&#xA;Had a CitySync discussion with Michael before he leaves for Vietnam.&#xA;I also tried out Reaper but didn&amp;rsquo;t get too far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-08</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:02:58 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/08/</guid>
      <description>Woke up early today and did cardio. Almost puked but the cold shower afterwards hit different.&#xA;Also super locked in at work.&#xA;Had K-BBQ at home for dinner with pork belly and organ meats.&#xA;I asked Jherzey to help me skin the cat and it definitely scared her. I did more after she left but my right shoulder started hurting. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to take it easy on the shoulder exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-07</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:32:24 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/07/</guid>
      <description>Pretty productive day!&#xA;Found a beat for focusing at work so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to sit in silence anymore.&#xA;I also tried out some online shopping haul with Jherzey after work before eating momos.&#xA;Just now, I set up Anki with Cantonese flashcards. I picked one without Chinese characters so I actually have to associate sounds to meaning.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been consistently waking up at 7 which means that I can finally get to sleep early (which is why I&amp;rsquo;m actually able to write before midnight now).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-06</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:19:35 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/06/</guid>
      <description>Went straight to University after meeting my friend David to tour the Gen Z gang around the campus.&#xA;It was pretty nice to go back to the places I used to study in pre-pandemic and tell them about it.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the exact spot where I studied for my first Math midterm. My heart was beating fast the whole time. Not sure if it was from nerves or from coffee&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;We used to do labs here until 8 pm&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-05</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:20:13 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/05/</guid>
      <description>Peeled a bunch of garlic cloves today.&#xA;Also went skating for a bit with Jherzey. Her skates were too small for her so we didn&amp;rsquo;t stay too long.&#xA;Also planned how much I would need to save up this year. It&amp;rsquo;s gonna be tough considering I still have one more major trip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-04</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:14:44 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/04/</guid>
      <description>Slept pretty much until the afternoon and then worked on CitySync stuff.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s already Sunday so I basically skipped 2 days of journalling. I definitely need to streamline this process. I could try using Obsidian for easier journalling and then automate the publishing process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-03</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:36 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/03/</guid>
      <description>Hung out with the Gen Z gang today (actually millennials).&#xA;Walked around downtown at -20°C which was fun.&#xA;Went hotpot and Hanjan which basically broke resolutions 1 &amp;amp; 3 but it&amp;rsquo;s all good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-02</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:01:29 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025/01/02/</guid>
      <description>I got my passport today so I am now legally allowed to leave the country 😌&#xA;I think I should start scheduling my off-work hours because I&amp;rsquo;m bad at time management and get distracted easily. It&amp;rsquo;s already past midnight that I&amp;rsquo;m writing on the journal.&#xA;EDIT:&#xA;I forgot to add why I wanted to do this in the first place. I found an old notebook of mine from 5+ years ago that had this entry:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 11:50:00 -0700</pubDate><author>cancheta.dev@gmail.com (Charles Ancheta)</author>
      <guid>https://charles.thyck.top/post/2025-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>Q1 Goals Some goals specific to my vacation this March, but also probably good to keep up for the rest of the year.&#xA;Lose weight (~5kg) - going to a wedding Brush up on Chinese - going to HK Not really required to get around, but one time I tried ordering bubble tea and couldn&amp;rsquo;t even say what I wanted Try to eat out less Lines up with Goal 1 and 2, since I&amp;rsquo;m going on a trip and need to save up The rest of the year The most generic resolutions you&amp;rsquo;ll find.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
